Hi! I'm

DIAN TRI BUDIANTO



ABOUT ME

My name is Dian Tri Budianto, and I'm 28 years old. I'm professional programmer. My Specialization are Web Developer and Mobile Application. I make sure I have qualification as your company needs. I've good motivation, I can work together with the team, my communication really good.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Php, JavaScript, Web Framework CI, Flutter, mobile apps native android using java, database mysql & postgree, Vue.Js, Java Spring Boot

SOCIAL











Kp. Bojong Nangka IV No.16. Pondok Gede - Bekasi

WORK EXPERIENCE

2020 - NOW:

PT BERCA HARDAYA PERKASA.

Develop E-Procurement web base using Generator jHipster, with **java** and **vueJS** and for management database with liquibase.

2016-2020:

PT HYUNDAI MOBIL INDONESIA.

Develop and Maintenance **Dealer Management System** web base

Develop and Maintenance Mobile Apps with **android native** and hybrid with framework **flutter** (Hyundai Mobil Apps on play store , Salesman Activity, Hyundai Asset, Hyundai Attendance, Service History).

2014-2016:

PT ANTA TIRTA KIRANA.

Develop website System Purchase Request and Purchase Order, System Weight Scale Monitoring, Job Work Order IT.

EDUCATION

2010-2014:

UNIVERSITAS SERANG RAYA.

Major. Informatics Engineering

Grade. S1 (3.50/4.00)

COURSE

2012: WEB DEVELOPER (HELP DESK TECHNOLOGY)

2013: WEB DESIGN FOUNDAMENTAL (WAHANA TRAINING)

2019: LINE FRONT-END FRAMEWORK (DICODING)

2019: LINE CHATBOOT (DICODING)

2019: FLUTTER FOUNDAMENTAL (UDACODING) **2019: FLUTTER** DEVELOPER EXPERT (DICODING)

2020: PYTHON BASIC (DICODING)

2020: BASIC **WEB** DESIGN (DICODING)

2020: FOUNDAMENTAL APLIKASI **ANDROID** (DICODING) **2020: FRONT-END** WEB DEVELOPMENT (DICODING)

2020: MEMBANGUN **PROGRESSIVE WEB APPS** (DICODING)

2020: DEV ANDROID JETPACK PRO (DICODING)

RECENT WORKS

- ✓ Web Apps: System Purchase Request, System Weight Scale
 Monitoring, System Work Order/ Ticketting
- ✓ **Mobile Apps**: Hyundai Mobil Apps, Salesman Activity, Hyundai Asset, Inquiry Service History, Ticketing Complaints Kosan
- ✓ **SKRIPSI** (SPK with Method Naive Bayes Web Base)
- ✓ System Perpustakaan, company profile, system penerimaan barang datang, vendor management, PR, PO
- ✓ Developer Android Studio Native & Hybrid Framework Flutter